[{"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 1], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 1], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}, {"body": [{"stem": "那两堆可以拼成下面的图形？用线连起来。", "imgSrc": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木5.svg", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木7.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木8.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木6.svg"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木1.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木9.svg"}, {"src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/积木/积木11.svg"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect4"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 0], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-6-7-05"}]